woorank.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy | WooRank.com

## Privacy

At WooRank, we are keenly aware of the trust you place in us and our responsibility to protect your privacy. As part of this responsibility, we are sharing with you what information we collect when you use our website analysis tool, why we collect it and how we use it to improve your experience. By using the WooRank web tool, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. 

###  Information Collection 

All data collected by the WooRank tool can be manually accessed by several other means publicly available online (Whois Lookup, Google Cached Pages, etc.). That is why every single report generated on www.woorank.com is considered 'public' and is thus stored in our database. Furthermore, it can be indexed by search engines. 

WooRank collects and uses website information to operate its website analysis tool and deliver the services you have requested. This information can include: IP address, domain names, estimated visitors, in-site and off-site SEO analysis, usability, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by WooRank for the operation of its service and to provide general statistics regarding use of the WooRank web tool. 

###  Use of Personal Information 

If you subscribe to our emails or newsletter WooRank may use your personally identifiable email address to inform you of other products or services available from WooRank and its affiliates. WooRank may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services. Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through the WooRank blog, this information may be collected and used by others. 

WooRank does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. WooRank may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, WooRank may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. Such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to WooRank, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. 

WooRank will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on WooRank or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of WooRank (including enforcing this agreement); and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of WooRank, or the public. 

###  Security of your Personal Information 

No method of safeguarding information is 100% secure. WooRank uses a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. WooRank secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. 

###  Changes to this Statement 

WooRank will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. WooRank encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how WooRank is protecting your information. When such a change is made, we will update the "Last Updated" date below. 

Last Updated: May 15, 2012.
